Watch full movies online for free at www.awooh.com
Hang on. I know.
You're doing so good.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Dr. Matthews to the nurses' station.
Excuse me.
My wife's in labor.
We called ahead for Dr. Wheeler.
I just need you to fill this out, please.
- Thank you.
- Have a seat, hon.
- I'll be right up.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Is this your first?
- No, no, it's our third.
Sir, can you sign here?
We're gonna name her Jessica.
Vitals look good.
Where's John?
- Where's my husband?
- Just relax now.
Everything's gonna be okay.
What's happening?
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry for your loss.
- What?
- Your baby's dead.
No, it's not dead. It's alive.
What are you talking about?
It's moving.
It's a terrible loss. We're so sorry.
- Just relax.
- No!
What? No, no, no. Put me to sleep.
I wanna be asleep.
- It's too late for that.
- No!
It's okay, you're doing great.
What are you doing?
You might feel some tugging.
Oh, my God. This isn't happening.
Congratulations, Mrs. Coleman.
It's a girl.
Yes, Kate, your dreams can be
a manifestation of your emotions.
It's your body and mind's way
of dealing...
...with the stress and grief
of what happened.
What if this has nothing to do
with the stillbirth?
What do you think it's about?
We're seeing kids
for the first time this weekend.
And maybe the nightmares...
Maybe I'm just not ready to adopt yet.
I drove by the wine shop
on the way home the other night.
Did you stop?
No. Wanted to. The thought
went through my brain, you know?
It wasn't for myself. It wasn't...
I just thought it would be nice to have
a bottle handy, in case we had guests.
But you didn't go in.
Mm-mm.
The key, to me...
...is not that you had the urge...
...but that you resisted it.
You wouldn't have made it through
the home study if you weren't ready.
But, ultimately...
...you have to decide.
Hi.
Honey, hello.
Let me see. Ooh. Did you paint this?
It's a beautiful butterfly.
It's fantastic.
Really wonderful. Good.
Let's go. I'm cold.
Are you okay?
Ah!
Max!
Stop throwing!
I'm working.
No, honey, I'm sorry.
Just take a break
for a little while, okay?
Because Mommy's trying
to play. Okay?
Daddy's here.
- Mine.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Sorry, practice went a little late.
- It's all right.
- Whoa.
- Okay, tough guy. Give me that.
- Wicked.
No, no.
Shoot it, shoot it. Go, go, go, go.
- No.
- Yes! Give me five.
Hey, how did it go? Daniel.
Fine.
Hey.
Okay.
Five minutes. I'm at the last level.
No more video games. Brush your teeth.
That's no fair. It won't save.
Come on, Dad, please?
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
God.
You smell good.
Okay.
All right.
I have to stop being like this.
I get it.
I'm very excited, I'm happy.
I get nervous.
I'm really scared.
Last time I felt all of this
was right before I lost the baby.
I don't want you to feel like we have
to go through with this for my sake.
It's not just... It's not for you.
I wanna take the love
we felt for Jessica...
...and I wanna give it to somebody
who really needs it.
Are you sure, hon?
Yes.
- Wanna make a snowman?
- Sure.
It's really cold out here.
Hey, stop it.
- Hi.
So glad you could make it.
- So are we.
- Yeah, finally, right?
- So good to see you.
- Thank you for coming.
- This is really something.
- So go take a look around.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Yeah, yeah.
Look at the snow orphan.
Snow orphan?
Uh, snorphan?
- Hey.
- No, show it to Sister Mary.
- Slow down, slow down.
- You can't catch me.
Yes, I can.
Hello?
Hi.
Are all these paintings yours?
- Yes. Do you like them?
- They're remarkable.
Thank you.
My name is Esther. What's yours?
John. Nice to meet you.
- Can I take a seat?
- Of course.
I never get tired of watching
these kids enjoy the party.
It really is. I'm so sorry
we didn't do this sooner.
Don't be. It's a big leap.
Adopting an older child
is not an easy decision to make.
John's in the bathroom.
Think he'll find us?
Do you wanna go look for him?
- Where did you get the idea for this one?
- My paintings always tell stories.
This one's about a sad mother lion
who can't find her cubs.
- She's smiling.
- She's dreaming about her babies.
It's the only thing
that makes her happy.
- I hope she finds them.
- She will. Look.
They were lost in the jungle,
and they were so scared...
...because they didn't have a mother.
Just when they thought
they'd be alone forever...
...they found their mother asleep
under this tree.
Now when she wakes up,
her dream will have come true.
- She'll have her family again.
- Amazing. You came up with that story?
- I think I hear his voice down here.
- Yes.
Hey. I want to introduce you.
This is my wife, Kate.
Kate, this is Esther.
Hello.
How are you? Nice to meet you.
She painted all these.
- Really?
- Yeah.
These are fantastic.
These are really wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Where did you learn how to do this?
I've just had lots of time to practice,
I guess.
It's really boring here.
It's boring here?
If you're so bored,
why aren't you down at the party?
I've never really seen the point of it.
Nobody's ever talked to me before.
I guess I'm different.
There's nothing wrong
with being different.
Well, you two have a lot in common.
I think people should always...
...try to take the bad things
that happen to them...
...and turn them into something good.
- Don't you?
- Yeah.
Absolutely.
She's originally from Russia, but
it's amazing how strong her English is.
She's only been in the country
a few years.
You get children from other countries?
It's rare. But when we do,
it's sometimes difficult to place them.
The family that brought her to America
died in a house fire.
In a fire?
My God.
Esther barely got out.
She's been through a lot,
but this is an extraordinary little girl.
She's very bright.
She's very mature for her age.
And she's very well-mannered.
She's a bit of a princess, actually.
She wears those ribbons on her wrists
and her neck all the time.
Mine too.
We had trouble with her
when we tried to take them off.
How does she get along
with other kids?
Oh, when she has to interact,
she's great.
Babe?
- She really did seem to open up with us.
- Yeah.
I thought she more
than opened up with you.
You seem to have made
quite a connection.
I could get the paperwork together
and see you back here in three weeks.
All right.
Okey-dokey.
Call me if you need anything.
Bye. Okay, thank you.
Oh, that's T-H.
T- H. Yeah.
And "Max" is like this?
Yeah.
Good.
- Is this your house?
- Now it's your house too.
Hi, sweetie. Hi. Look who's here.
Hello, Max. My name is Esther.
She's been practicing the whole way.
- Can she hear?
- A little.
She was born almost completely deaf.
That just allows her to hear enough
to read lips.
That's all right, I got it.
I'd like to introduce you
to Grandma Barbara.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
That's precious.
It's a pleasure to meet you too.
Danny.
This is Esther.
Hello, Daniel.
Hey.
Why does she dress like that?
- Come on. Stop it.
- I'm just asking a question.
Oh!
- You have a piano?
- Yeah.
- Would you like to learn how to play?
- I would love to.
Do you like it?
- It's perfect.
- Good.
Thank you.
How do you say "thank you"?
Wow, look at that.
What? What? What?
Dad, look.
- Dad.
- Where did you get that?
- Dad, look, I'm killing Trevor.
- Great.
Yes.
Thank you.
Come on, Dad. My solo's gonna end.
Hurry, look.
Wow, cool.
- Trevor, you suck.
- Shut up.
That's fabulous.
Come on, guys. This is lame.
I was just about to beat you.
I'm glad you like it, honey.
Come on, guys.
Hurry up, I'm freezing my ass off.
- Dude, it's all in here.
- Oh, God. My hands are freezing.
Oh, man, she's hot.
- Move over, man.
- Page 34 will change your life.
Whoa.
This looks like your mom.
No.
Esther and Maxine
seem to be getting along well.
Yeah.
How's she doing, Kate?
Esther's fitting right in.
I meant Maxine.
She's playing by the pond
like nothing ever happened.
She doesn't remember, does she?
No. She's fine.
So, what are your plans?
You know,
probably get Esther settled...
...then go back to teaching.
Thought they weren't gonna
take you back.
No, I'm not talking about Yale.
I'll just... I'll probably give lessons
from home.
That's too bad.
That was a very good job.
Well, I didn't quit because I wanted to.
I know.
You had to have your moment of clarity.
That is an A.A. term.
And I didn't go to A.A.
I just stopped drinking.
Same difference.
We all need a wake-up call sometimes.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Come here.
Yeah?
- Oh, hey.
- We're scared of the lightning.
Oh, come in.
- I wanna sleep next to Daddy.
- Hang on.
Okay.
I'm gonna call later,
make sure everything's okay.
Okay. They're gonna love your design.
- You gonna pick up the phone?
- Yeah.
All right.
Esther?
Come on.
Esther, come on, we gotta go!
You gotta be kidding me.
Wow. Uh...
- Will you please go wait in the car?
- Come on.
Sweetheart,
this isn't really a school dress.
But I like it.
Don't you think it's pretty?
Yes, it's so beautiful...
...but I just don't think
you're gonna be comfortable in it.
What about those jeans?
You're afraid the other children
will laugh at me.
I thought you said there wasn't
anything wrong with being different.
Yes, you're right.
You're absolutely right.
Okay. Have fun.
Take a seat, please. Take a seat.
Don't make me ask again, please.
Okay, this is our new student.
Her name's Esther Coleman.
And I'd like you all
to make her feel very welcome today.
Oh, look. Little Bo Peep texted me.
She wants her outfit back.
Okay, go take a seat.
Okay, if everybody could turn
to Page 27...
No!
No! Esther, what are you doing?
Get away from there! No!
You don't play near the water!
You know that!
Come on, get out!
Max.
Sweet. Bull's-eye.
Got you.
- Did you kill it?
- I didn't think it would hurt him.
Put it out of its misery.
- It's in pain, and it's your responsibility.
- It was just an accident.
If you walk away now,
it'll starve to death.
Is that what you want?
I'm not doing it.
It's all right.
- It's in heaven now.
- What's wrong with you?
- Is the water warm enough?
- Yes, thank you.
Okay. Call me if you need anything.
Esther?
Esther.
Open this door.
- What are you doing?
- I always lock the door.
No, we don't lock doors in this house.
But what if someone comes in
and sees me?
Nobody's gonna come in.
Look, I'm gonna stand right here,
if that's what you want.
I could sing for you.
I used to sing for the sisters
so they would know I was all right.
Okay.
All right. But you know what?
This is just for tonight.
Your parents must have gone
to a lot of retard camps to find her.
Watch it.
Are you okay?
Is this a Bible?
Jesus Freak brought a Bible
to school today.
Hey, wanna come over?
- Good one.
- Your sister's a total spaz.
She's not my sister.
I can't believe you did that.
Oh, little doggy.
Is this your collar, little doggy?
Not A. A, B.
You did really good.
No, I didn't. I made like 11 mistakes.
I'll do better next time.
Your teacher told me
what happened today.
Don't you want to talk about it?
There's nothing to talk about.
You know I'm here for you, right?
You know that, right?
I got something I wanna show you.
I have one just like this
that I use as a diary.
And I thought that maybe you
and I could use this one...
...for a scrapbook.
That's Mommy and Daddy
on their wedding day.
That's Daniel, Christmas morning.
Here's Max.
And there's you.
Who's Jessica?
Max talks about her.
"I never held you, but I feel you.
You never spoke, but I hear you.
I never knew you, but I love you."
What happened to her?
She died
while she was still in my tummy.
But we scattered her ashes here.
And as long as this plant grows...
...then part of her
will be alive inside it.
She would have been lucky.
You're a great mommy.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Thank you. It means a lot.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
It's very interesting.
Esther started to open up today.
That's very interesting.
I'm starting to feel
like there's a real connection.
Me too.
- No, honey, not here.
- Shh.
They're sleeping.
Baby, come here,
you'll like it, believe me.
- Okay, let's get down to business.
- No, no, no.
Okay, just for a second, then.
Yeah.
- No, no, no.
- Come on.
I have to. Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah.
- Ow!
- Oh, sorry.
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus, honey. Damn it.
Esther?
We have to talk about last night.
- Do we?
- Yes, we do.
See, there are certain things
that grown-ups do...
...that children aren't supposed to see.
And that was one of them.
Esther, listen to me.
When grown-ups love each other
very, very much...
...they wanna show each other
that love. Express it.
I know. They fuck.
She could've picked it up anywhere.
Probably at school.
This wasn't something she overheard.
I mean, she knew what it meant.
Huh.
And, babe,
the way she said it is...
I don't even think she expected
to get in trouble over it.
Well, we'll talk to her about it tonight.
Fine.
Well, what did you have in mind?
No, I thought we could take her
to Dr. Browning.
I don't think we need to take her
to the shrink quite yet.
Well, you know,
we just don't know that much about her.
The family she stayed with
could've been like:
"Pass the fucking potatoes"
at dinnertime, you know?
If she's saying it to my face, what
is she saying when we're not there?
I don't want her exerting
that kind of influence over Max.
Anyway, I just don't want to make
a big deal out of one little dirty word.
Fine. Fucking spend some time
with her, then.
All right, bitch.
Let's have a snow fight!
Come on, no throwing snowballs.
Hey, neighbor.
- Hey.
- Haven't seen you around lately.
I've been pretty busy.
Has the homeowners' association
been soldiering on without me?
It's not the same.
Um, actually, I had a favor to ask.
I have a chair
that I need moved upstairs...
...and I was hoping you could come by
and help me with that sometime.
Yeah.
- Yeah, sure.
- Good.
Maybe Kate and I could help you out.
Just let us know.
I'll call you.
Let's go, honey.
Okay, I'm watching you.
Brenda's father says
that you pushed her.
That's not true.
We were just playing.
I swear.
- Okay.
- And did you see what happened?
What? Mom, what's she saying?
She wants you to pass the bread
and butter.
- Wasn't asking you.
- Hey, now.
Can you eat normal?
I am eating normal.
Yeah, maybe in Transylvania,
or whatever country you're from.
Incidentally, I'm from Russia.
Transylvania isn't even a country.
It's a part of Romania.
You are such a freak.
- Hey.
- Hey, Danny.
I don't want any more talk like that.
But why does she have to act
like that?
All my friends make fun of me
because of her.
Maybe you need different friends.
Maybe you should send her back
to the retard camp.
- Daniel.
Apologize to your sister.
She's not my fucking sister.
I got it.
Okay.
That's me.
You get the key back
when you say you're sorry.
Is there anything special
you want me to make tonight?
You have any favorites?
Hello.
- Well, how are you?
- Hi, we're great. We're doing good.
- How is she?
- She's here, hold on.
Hey, Sister Abigail.
Do you wanna say hello?
- Come on. Esther, just quickly say hi.
- I said, no.
You know what, do you mind, darling,
can you get five apples for me?
Sorry, she got shy all of a sudden.
It's all right.
I'm just calling to remind you...
...that I'm gonna need her medical...
...and dental charts
for my supervision report.
She's not thrilled about the dentist.
How is everyone doing?
Is she opening up to you?
I guess you can say that. She dropped
the F-bomb on me a few weeks ago.
I guess she's finally
coming out of her shell.
Yeah.
Any other glitches I should know of?
We had a big one recently.
It's a girl named Brenda at school.
They were at the playground,
there was a slide, well, she fell off.
Esther may have pushed her down.
I'm not getting the story straight,
but she got hurt.
Is she all right?
Luckily. She broke her ankle
and had something like six stitches.
That doesn't sound too lucky.
Well, she's lucky
she didn't break her neck.
You told me
you didn't know how to play.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
You offered to teach me
and I accepted.
Okay. So then you were
just pretending this whole time?
I thought
you would enjoy teaching me.
It must be frustrating for someone
who loves music as much as you...
...to have a son who isn't interested
and a daughter who can't even hear.
Wait, wait, wait.
I walk in on her playing Tchaikovsky
without a mistake.
I mean, she's been lying to me
this whole time.
She just wants to spend time
with you. It's hardly a lie.
You wouldn't know.
You wouldn't.
She's on her best behavior with you.
She's completely different with me.
So, what are you saying?
I don't know.
She threw a fit at school.
She pushed Brenda at the playground.
- Now you're saying that was her fault?
- I don't know. Honey, I don't know.
I wasn't there.
You were watching them.
Oh, come on. It was an accident.
Okay, let's not blame her
for anything, fine.
I'll take her word for everything.
Should I just believe what she said
about you and Joyce too?
What did she say?
- She says that you were hitting on her.
- What?
Oh, come on. She must've
misunderstood. It was, like...
Did she invite you over?
She asked me
to help her move a chair.
- She did?
- Yeah. I blew her off.
Oh, God.
Why didn't you tell me?
- I...
- We could've laughed about it.
- No, I knew how...
- You were hiding it.
Honey, I knew how you'd react.
Kate. Kate.
You can't get jealous of every woman
that I talk to, right?
- It's been like 10 years.
- What does that mean?
You say that
like it actually means something.
It's only been two years
since you told me.
You know how sorry I am. I just feel
like I've earned a little trust here.
- I gave you a second chance.
- That's not fair. That's not fair.
Let me get this straight. We can talk
about my mistakes, not yours?
I was sick! You were an asshole
who wanted to fuck somebody else!
You put our child's life in danger.
I could've walked away months ago.
Nobody would've blamed me.
Oh, that's sharp. That's sharp. Where
did you get that from, your mother?
Danny. Turn that crap down, please,
I gotta work.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
I'll get it.
- Hello, Esther.
- What are you doing here?
May I come in?
I'm afraid I may have made a mistake.
There could be something wrong
with Esther.
What?
What? You told us that you'd never
had any trouble with her.
I didn't. But trouble does have a way
of finding her.
What kind of trouble?
Two girls get into a fight, there she is.
Someone gets caught stealing,
there she is again.
- So? Does that mean...?
- Just let her finish.
After you told me about the girl in
the playground, I called her old school.
While she was there,
there was a boy...
...who fell with scissors in his hand...
...and accidentally stabbed himself
through the jaw.
And Esther was there again.
I don't understand.
He accidentally stabbed himself.
But the most troubling thing
is the Sullivan house fire.
I checked into it further. It was arson.
They have never found the person
who did it.
What are you suggesting here?
That she had anything to do
with any of this?
It's ridiculous.
That a child could commit such crimes...
...it flies in the face
of everything I believe.
Well, yeah.
There's a mean lady here.
She's come to take me away.
Will you help me?
We've had
some behavioral problems, but...
Yeah, nothing like that. I mean, right?
- Yes, we have.
- Really, hon, think about it.
I've tried to reach the Russian
orphanage where she was raised.
I think we need to know
what we're dealing with.
Well, I'll tell you
- No, you know what?
- Stop it. Listen.
We're dealing with a 9-year-old girl
who's an orphan, okay?
- We're taking her to Dr. Browning.
- We can take her to Dr. Browning.
Do you want to play?
I'll call you
as soon as I find anything else out.
- Right. Take care.
- Okay. Thank you very much.
Maybe later.
It's going to be fine.
We'll scare her so bad
she'll never come back here.
Here she comes.
Wave your arms and make her stop.
Max, go.
You all right? Max?
Max?
You okay?
Stop crying.
Grab a foot
and help me get her off the road.
Now.
Help me hide her.
That doesn't matter.
They'll send you to jail
just for helping me hide her.
I had to kill her
because she was going to tell on me.
You're not going to tell on me.
Are you?
Don't worry.
You're my little sister.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I love you.
Tell me what you saw.
- What are you doing?
- What did you see?
I saw you and Max in the tree house.
What else?
- What do you mean?
- What else did you see?
I didn't see anything. I swear.
- Did you tell anyone?
- No.
I didn't tell anyone.
Please...
If I find out that you're lying,
I'll cut your hairless little prick off...
...before you even figure out
what it's for.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
You pissed yourself.
It was nice talking to you, Alice.
I hope we can be friends.
I'd like that.
- We'll be right out, honey.
- You can come on in.
My initial instinct is that...
...there's not a deeply-rooted problem
in Esther's past.
- So there's nothing wrong with her?
- No.
It's not all good news.
I think what needs to be examined...
...is Esther's relationship
with those around her.
Specifically with you, Kate.
It seems she feels there's been some
real tension between the two of you.
- Okay.
- She's doing her best to please you...
...but you're blocking her attempts
to bond.
That's not true. That's not true at all.
I've done everything.
- Right?
- Just let her finish.
Something's happening
to cause Esther to feel this way.
Perhaps it's your guilt about drinking
or what happened to Max.
Maybe some of your feelings
of inadequacy as a mother...
...are manifesting themselves
in your relationship with Esther.
I don't feel inadequate.
What did she tell you?
She didn't see. She doesn't know.
She's so stupid.
Esther's a very shy, reserved...
...sensitive little girl going through
an extremely difficult time.
She's exceptionally bright
and highly articulate.
She just needs a little patience
and understanding.
Thanks for your support back there.
That was your idea.
Kate, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not a psychiatrist,
but a lot of what she said made sense.
Do you wanna get that?
- Hello?
- Hello, is this Mrs. Coleman?
Yes. Who's this?
This is Sister Judith
from St. Mariana's.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I need to know...
...if Sister Abigail
made it to her appointment with you.
Yes. Why?
She hasn't returned since yesterday...
... and I'm just starting
to get really worried.
Charlie 24,
you wanna hold them there?
Hey.
Okay, I think we're done.
Detective, do you have any leads
or suspects?
- No, not yet.
- I just don't understand...
...this kind of thing.
Who would do this? It's...
Awful.
You think of anything else,
you give us a call.
Yes. Absolutely.
Let's go.
This is what Sister Abigail
was talking about. Look.
"Character-disturbed children."
Look at the symptoms.
"Superficially charming. Difficulty
at making and keeping friends."
I'm not sure this is what she meant.
She could've told Dr. Browning
whatever she wanted to hear. Look.
They "are adroit manipulators...
...oftentimes playing people off
one another to get what they want."
Well, you gonna show this
to Dr. Browning?
I'm not showing her anything.
I'm not seeing her anymore.
- When did you decide that?
- When do you think?
You're gonna discount Dr. Browning?
Why does everyone get the benefit
of the doubt from you except for me?
If you need help with the kids,
we can arrange that.
I don't need help.
I just wanna know more about her.
I wanna know where she came from,
and I wanna know who she is.
What if Sister Abigail was right?
I mean, if someone was in danger,
our own children...
...wouldn't you wanna know?
- Of course I would.
I'll contact the orphanage she came from
in Russia. All right?
I mean, it's a start.
- What?
- Hey.
Fine.
I was wondering if you'd heard from
anyone at the Sludyanka Shelter.
Sister Abigail had mentioned
that she would...
Oh, you did.
I don't understand. How can they have
no record of her being there?
Yes, please.
Could you just call me as soon as
you know anything, please? Thank you.
Esther, we gotta go.
Esther?
You got me.
- What?
- I don't want to go to the dentist.
- Why not?
- I just don't want to go.
- What, are you scared?
- No.
We're gonna reschedule, though.
Tell you what, I'll let you play hooky
if you want to come and draw with me.
All right.
Wait, Daniel.
How are you two getting along
with Esther?
Fine, I guess.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, Mom.
But has she ever made you feel,
I don't know, uncomfortable...
...or has she done anything
that she's not supposed to do?
- No.
- Like, has she ever hurt any of you?
No.
You sure?
Okay. All right.
I like it when it's just the two of us.
You don't know how long I've waited
for a daddy just like you.
Mommy too, right?
I don't think
Mommy likes me very much.
Hey.
- That is not true. Mommy loves you.
- It's all right.
It must be hard to love an adopted child
as much as your own.
Sweetheart, you're just as much a part
of this family as Danny and Max. Okay?
Do something nice for Mommy.
Show her how much you love her.
That's a wonderful idea.
I have a special surprise
for you, Mommy.
You do?
I picked these flowers just for you.
- Esther, what did you do? God.
- My arm!
- Why did you do this?
- Daddy, my arm!
- John!
- Hey.
- What did you do?
- Hey. Stop, stop.
Why did you do this?
- Oh, God. God, she did this on purpose.
- No, no, no.
- Yes, she did.
- Hey. Honey, no.
She knew
what these roses meant to me.
It's my fault, hon. I told her
to do something nice for you.
I can't believe this.
Daddy!
Daddy, Daddy!
What is it, honey?
My arm still hurts.
Can I have a look at it?
You're okay.
I'll be gentle. It's all right, honey.
Oh, my God.
We need to take you to the hospital.
You're a brave little girl,
you know that?
Doctor said
you're gonna heal real fast, okay?
You broke her arm.
It's impossible.
I didn't grab her that hard.
She wants to sleep in here tonight.
Maybe you should sleep downstairs.
I'm having guests for dinner.
You know, you can have it. Thanks.
Have a good day.
Daniel.
Your books.
- What happened? Let me see your bag.
- I don't know.
We just bought this.
Pick it up, it's gonna get wet.
Mom!
Max! No! Help!
Max!
Are you okay?
I'm here. Mommy's here.
You're okay, honey. Come on.
I got you. Yeah. Oh, baby, it's okay.
I'm so sorry.
I remember I put it in park
and I set the brake.
Max didn't indicate
that Esther did anything.
Well, Max is covering for her.
And I don't think it's the first time.
It also wouldn't be the first time
you blamed Esther for your own mistake.
You know what?
I want her out of this house.
You're ready for somebody
to come and take her?
I am. I don't care.
I will do whatever it takes
to protect my children.
The girls found this this morning.
The girls found it.
You mean Esther found it.
Yes, Esther. Does it make
any difference? Is she lying?
You need help.
We've reserved a place for you
in a rehabilitation facility...
...about 45 minutes from here.
I didn't drink it.
I bought two bottles.
I poured one of them down the sink.
- But not this one?
- No.
John, I haven't had a drink
in almost a year.
We wanna help you,
but there's nothing we can do...
...until you stop lying to yourself.
- I'm not lying. I wanted to drink it.
You have no fucking idea how badly
I wanted to drink it, but I didn't.
- I didn't drink it.
- If Max had gotten hurt...
What happened this morning
has nothing to do with this.
I find that hard to believe.
The only reason that I'm sober
is because of Max and Daniel.
I think about what would have happened
had you not been there...
...and it makes me wanna kill myself.
I would never do anything...
...to let something like that
ever happen again. I wouldn't.
That is so manipulative.
I know I haven't given you reason
to believe me, I know I haven't.
I lied to you.
I should have told you about this.
I'll go to therapy, I'll go to fucking A.A.
if that's what you want...
...but you have to believe me.
- I don't.
You have to believe me.
John, you have to trust me on this.
I'll give you a week to go to rehab...
...or I'm leaving
and I'm taking the kids with me.
I think that's fair, okay?
I'll help you as much as I can,
make it really easy.
Mom's gonna come in the afternoon.
All right? I'm willing to do this.
I'm willing to try and figure this out.
- But it's up to you.
- I'll shoot Mommy if you tell.
Max. Max, are you okay?
What did she do? Did she do something
to make the car crash?
If you saw her, you have to help me,
so Mom and Dad can protect us.
Why not?
Is that Sister Abigail?
Max. What did she do
in my tree house?
Are the bad things still there?
Everything's gonna be okay.
I'll get the stuff from the tree house.
Then they'll have to believe us.
- Going somewhere, Kate?
- What are you doing here?
She's fine. Let's not wake her.
Go to your room.
Honestly, we're past that now.
Aren't we?
I know what you're doing.
I will not let you hurt my children.
Me?
I'm not the one who passed out drunk
and let Max almost drown in the pond.
If it wasn't for John...
...she'd be dead,
and you'd probably still be in jail.
Who told you that?
It's very intimate.
- I learned so much.
- Give it to me.
- Jessica. Your cheating husband.
- Esther, give it to me.
Where you hide your wine bottles.
I'm... I'm warning you right now.
"She was still kicking
when the doctor told me...
...it was something called phantom...
...fetal movement.
- For 16 days, I carried my dead baby."
- Stop it. Esther.
"It was the cruelest torture
I could imagine."
Stop it. You stop it.
What's wrong with you?
Kate, it's too late. It's your own fault.
You took your family for granted.
- What do you mean?
- What are you going to do?
Hit me?
We adopted her from you.
How could you not know anything?
The Sullivans
could have adopted her illegally.
She doesn't remember anything
that could help us?
I'm gonna call you back.
"Saarne Institute."
Hello. Do you speak English?
Do you speak English?
Is there anyone
who speaks English there?
This is very important.
I don't know what you're saying.
- Hello?
- Is this the Saarne Institute?
Yes.
Yes. I need to talk to somebody
about one of your children.
She was adopted by an American family.
It's a girl.
She is not come from here.
Well, I haven't even
told you her name yet.
You do not understand.
Saarne Institute is not an orphanage.
It is a mental hospital.
Are you looking for this?
Poor Sister Abigail.
I couldn't have done it myself,
you know. Max is just as guilty as I am.
- Whatever Max did, you made her do it.
- Think about it.
How did she even know
what was up here?
It's always better
to burn the evidence.
If they find these things,
they won't just be coming for me.
They'll be coming for Max too.
- Is that really what you want?
- Wait.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Mom!
It's called the Saarne Institute.
S- A-A-R-N-E, Saarne.
It's in Estonia.
Estonia? No, this can't be right.
All of her paperwork is from Russia.
I'm sending them a picture
of her right now.
Maybe her birth mother
was a patient there.
I don't know.
Maybe she was even born there.
Mom!
Help!
Mom! Dad!
Oh, God!
Oh, God. Call 911!
Don't worry. You're going to heaven.
Oh, God!
Oh, my God! Daniel!
Move away! Move away from the fire!
Daniel?
Oh, God, no. Daniel?
Mommy's right here. Can you hear me?
Please wake up.
Honey, Mommy's right here, okay?
You're gonna be all right.
We stopped the abdominal bleeding,
but he has a very serious neck injury.
He's stabilized for now. You should
consider yourselves very lucky.
- Can we see him?
- In a little while.
He's resting in the ICU.
Okay. And will he be able to tell us
what happened?
It's possible.
No way of knowing for sure
what he'll remember until he wakes up.
Excuse me.
It's gonna be okay.
I know you're exhausted
and upset, and so am I.
There has to be some other explanation.
She didn't come from an insane asylum.
The orphanage you thought
she came from has never heard of her.
Everything about her could be a lie.
We have her passport. We have
school records, medical records.
These are papers
from around the world.
What is this? It's a piece of paper.
Your own mother was there this time. It
wasn't just me. Your mother was there.
It's either Esther
or Daniel who started the fire.
- Who do you think it was?
- I don't know.
I'm so done.
I'm done connecting these dots for you.
You know, you can think
whatever you want about me.
I will leave tonight. If that's
what you want, I will leave tonight.
On one condition. Esther goes too.
Can I have a dollar
for the soda machine?
Your mother wants you
to stay right there.
There you go. Don't be too long.
Okay.
What? What is it, sweetie?
Code 99, ICU.
- Coming through, coming through.
- Mom, take Max.
Let's go, Room 304! Crash
cart coming through! Move, people!
- Daniel?
- Clear the hall! Clear the hall!
You have to stay out here.
He's in cardiac arrest. Stay out here.
Daniel!
- Here we go.
- Start a drip.
- Check BP, please.
- Check ventilation.
Oh, God.
We got a pulse. We got a pulse.
Kate.
What did you do?
What did you do to him, you bitch?
Stop, stop!
- Orderlies!
- She's trying to kill my baby!
- Daddy!
- Hold her!
She's trying to kill my baby!
Hold her still.
Get off me.
Hold her still. Hold her still.
Okay. Easy, easy.
- You okay?
- There you go.
- Kate.
- Daniel.
They're running tests.
We should know more tomorrow.
Don't worry about Daniel.
He'll be okay.
He'll be home in a few days.
You need to stay here, get some rest.
I'm gonna take Max and Esther home.
Johnny.
Please don't let her near Max.
I love you.
Hello, Daddy.
- What are you wearing?
- Do you like it?
Oh, Jesus.
Look at you. What have you done
to your face? What is this?
I don't want to be alone. I'm scared.
I love you, Daddy.
You too, hon.
I really love you.
I know.
John, let me take care of you.
What are you doing?
What's gotten into you, huh?
What's going on?
You said you loved me.
You are so confused.
You know what?
I don't love you like that.
That's the way Kate and I
love each other.
You understand?
I don't see that.
- You have to respect your mother.
- I do.
I just feel like I'm alone sometimes
in respecting you.
I don't think anyone ever thinks
about what you might be feeling.
I really care about you, John.
Yeah, I know, Esther.
I'm just... I'm tired.
I'm very tired.
And I don't know what to do.
It's difficult.
I mean,
everything is just falling apart...
...and, oh, my God,
I'm so worried for Daniel.
Oh, God.
You're a good person, John.
You're a great father.
And a handsome man.
Jesus Christ!
My God, stop, stop, stop!
Just stop talking and go upstairs!
Go to your room!
- Stop talking to me like I'm a child.
- I'm calling Sister Judith tomorrow.
We're gonna have a conversation
about your future in this house.
I just... I can't do it anymore.
Fine.
Esther.
- Hello?
- Is this Katherine Coleman?
- Yeah. This is she.
My name is Dr. Vنrava.
I'm calling from the Saarne Institute.
- I've just seen the picture you e-mailed.
- And do you recognize her?
Where is she right now? Is she
someplace where she can hear you?
No, she's not with me.
She's with my husband at home.
Call your husband right now, and tell him
to get your family out of the house.
- And then call the police.
- He won't listen to me. But why?
Then tell him the little girl in the picture
is not really a little girl.
- She's a grown woman.
- What?
What are you talking about?
The picture I sent you...
... is of our adopted daughter,
and she's 9 years old.
No, she's not.
She has a rare hormone disorder.
It's called hypopituitarism.
It causes proportional dwarfism.
She only looks like a child.
According to our records,
Leena Klammer was born in 1976.
She's 33 years old.
This can't be. This is a mistake.
I hope so, for your sake.
Does she have the scars?
What? I don't know. What scars?
Leena was one
of our most violent patients.
When she was here,
she was kept in a straitjacket...
... to stop her from hurting our staff.
She was constantly fighting
to get out.
It cut into her skin and left her
with scars around her wrists and neck.
There is no way
you could not have seen them.
Why was she at your hospital?
She's dangerously ill, violent.
She killed seven people that we know of.
Oh, my God. How could she fool us?
She has been passing herself off
as a little girl for most of her life.
She tricked a family here in Estonia
into adopting her.
When she couldn't seduce the father,
she killed him and his whole family.
- Then she burned the house down.
- Yes. How did you know?
She disappeared a year ago
and we lost track of her.
If it's really Leena,
you don't have much time.
Esther?
Come on, Johnny. Come on.
Pick up the fucking phone.
Shit.
Come on.
Oh, God!
911. What is your emergency?
I need the police.
We have an intruder in our home.
Come on.
This is John.
- John?
You've reached my cell,
but I can't pick up.
Oh, fuck it.
John?
John? John?
No, God!
Max.
What the fuck?
Esther! Don't you hurt her!
Leave her alone! I'm here!
Esther!
I know.
Go back. It's too dangerous. Go back.
Please.
Don't let me die, Mommy.
I'm not your fucking Mommy!
Baby, it's okay.
Watch full movies online for free at www.awooh.com